RG 002:025, Committee on Commerce
Connecticut State Library
Commerce Committee records
1993-1997
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Commerce
.5 cubic feet
The Commerce Committee has cognizance of all matters relating to the Department of Economic and Community Development, the Connecticut Development Authority and Connecticut Innovations, Incorporated. Consists of meeting documents including notices, agendas, minutes, attendance, and roll calls; bill books, and correspondence.
RG002_025_COM
1999-073
Historical Note
The Commerce Committee has cognizance of all matters relating to the Department of Economic and Community Development, the Connecticut Development Authority and Connecticut Innovations, Incorporated.
Scope and Content
Consists of meeting documents including notices, agendas, minutes, attendance, and roll calls; bill books, and correspondence.
Arrangement
Arranged by year.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Commerce -- Connecticut; Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Commerce -- Records and correspondence; Tourism -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas (administrative records); Correspondence; Minutes; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- 1993
  - Report on deploying adavanced manufacturing technology prepared by Connecticut Innovations, Inc., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1994
  - Attendance sheets, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bills, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Notices, agendas, and minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Roll call and vote tally sheets, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tourism Subcommittee meeting notices and minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1995
  - Attendance sheets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Membership list, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Notices, agendas, and minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Roll call and vote tally sheets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Internatinal Trade Council agendas and minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tourism Subcommittee notices, agendas, and minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1996
  - Attendance sheets, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bills, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Notices, agendas, and minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Roll call votes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tourism Subcommittee notices, agendas, and minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 1997
  - Agendas and minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tourism Subcommittee agendas and minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)